(Amy:)This is a portable
electroencephalogram.
(Amy:)I'm doing research
on emotions and brain activity.
(Amy:)So when you start crying,
(Amy:)I can see which region
of the brain is activated.
(Amy:)Then I'm going to stimulate
the analogous area
(Amy:)in the brain of a rhesus monkey
and see if he cries.
(Amy:)Cool, huh?
(Howard:)I choose you.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Howard:)Yep. I moved out
of my mother's house.
(Howard:)Cord is cut.
(Howard:)I'm all yours.
(Bernadette:)What did she say
when you told her?
(Howard:)I don't know. She hasn't
responded to my email yet.
(Bernadette:)This is so great.
(Bernadette:)I love you, Howard.
(Howard:)I love you, too.
(Howard:)So what's for dinner?
(Bernadette:)Well, I don't really have much
of anything in the house.
(Howard:)That's fine.